{
    "part": [
        {
            "title": "Part1 - 中2レベル1",
            "exercises": [
                {
                    "question": "ボクと契約して、魔法少女になってよ!",
                    "answer": "Make a contract with me, and become a Magical Girl!"
                },
                {
                    "question": "問おう。貴方が私のマスターか?",
                    "answer": "I ask you. Are you my master?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "私はその幻想を壊そうと思います。",
                    "answer": "I'll destroy the illusion of yours!"
                },
                {
                    "question": "今のはメラゾーマではありません。メラです。",
                    "answer": "It is not Kafrizzle. It is my frizz."
                },
                {
                    "question": "パンツじゃないから恥ずかしくないもん！",
                    "answer": "These are not panties. They are pants! No problem."
                },
                {
                    "question": "まったく、小学生は最高だぜ！",
                    "answer": "Jeez, elementary kids are amazing!"
                },
                {
                    "question": "「見せよう」ガッツは静かに言う。「最高とは何なのか、を」",
                    "answer": "I'll Show you,\"guts cool say, \"what is SAIKO.\""
                },
                {
                    "question": "何故そこで愛！？",
                    "answer": "Why do you say \"Love\" now?!"
                },
                {
                    "question": "さすがはお兄様です",
                    "answer": "That's great as expected, my brother."
                },
                {
                    "question": "これは、ゲームであっても、遊びではない",
                    "answer": "Even if this is a game, it is not play."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Part2 - 中2レベル2",
            "exercises": [
                {
                    "question": "「これはゾンビですか？　それとも魔法少女ですか？」「はい。魔法少女です」",
                    "answer": "\"Is this a zombie or a magical girl? Yes.\" \"It is a magical girl\""
                },
                {
                    "question": "情けなさだけならグローバル級ね！",
                    "answer": "Only your miserableness is world-class!"
                },
                {
                    "question": "完全にフルハウス",
                    "answer": "It is perfectly \"Full House\"."
                },
                {
                    "question": "「空のあれらは何ですか？」「パンティーの群れです」",
                    "answer": "What are those in the sky? They are \"flying panties\"."
                },
                {
                    "question": "ジャッジメントですの！",
                    "answer": "I am a \"Judgement\"."
                },
                {
                    "question": "もう、何も怖くない",
                    "answer": "I'm not afraid of anything anymore."
                },
                {
                    "question": "ルカはとてもかわいい。だが、男だ。",
                    "answer": "Ruka is very cute. But he is a man."
                },
                {
                    "question": "彼女はいつもにニコニコあなたの後ろに居ます",
                    "answer": "She is always behind you with keeping smile."
                },
                {
                    "question": "「市民、幸福ですか？」「はい、私は完璧に幸福です」",
                    "answer": "\"Citizen, are you happy?\" \"Yes, I am perfectly happy.\""
                },
                {
                    "question": "幸福なのは義務なんです♪",
                    "answer": "Happiness is mandatory."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Part3 - 中2レベル3",
            "exercises": [
                {
                    "question": "あぁー心がぴょんぴょんするんじゃーっ",
                    "answer": "Ah＾ My Mind is hopping."
                },
                {
                    "question": "そんなのないよ。あり得えません",
                    "answer": "It does not exist. No way."
                },
                {
                    "question": "特技は肉を削ぎ落とすことです",
                    "answer": "My special ability is to slice off a meat."
                },
                {
                    "question": "「彼女は私の二次元嫁です。」「いいえ、私のです。」",
                    "answer": "\"She is Mai Waifu.\" \"No, she is mine.\""
                },
                {
                    "question": "「誰だ貴様！？」「とっくにご存知なんだろう？」",
                    "answer": "\"Who are you?\" \"You already know, don't you?\""
                },
                {
                    "question": "別にあれを倒してしまっても構わんのだろう？",
                    "answer": "It doesn’t matter if I defeat that one?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "その金ピカの男はたくさんの宝を持っている",
                    "answer": "The gold man has many treasures."
                },
                {
                    "question": "ホモが嫌いな女子なんかいません",
                    "answer": "No woman doesn't like gay men!"
                },
                {
                    "question": "あなたのサーヴァントは武器をいくつ持っていますか？",
                    "answer": "How many weapons dose your servant have?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "今期の彼の嫁は何人ですか？",
                    "answer": "How many waifu does he have in this season?"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Part4 - 中2レベル4",
            "exercises": [
                {
                    "question": "この中に１人妹がいる！",
                    "answer": "There is a sister in this members."
                },
                {
                    "question": "イメージしろ！",
                    "answer": "Picture it."
                },
                {
                    "question": "「我のものとなれ、勇者よ！」「断る！」",
                    "answer": "\"Become mine, HERO!\" \"I refuse!\""
                },
                {
                    "question": "静まれ、俺の右腕よ。",
                    "answer": "Calm down my right hand."
                },
                {
                    "question": "お前の勝手なイメージを押し付けるな！",
                    "answer": "Don't push your personal images on me."
                },
                {
                    "question": "パパのいうことを聞きなさい！",
                    "answer": "Listen to me girls. I am your father!"
                },
                {
                    "question": "その緑の髪の少女はとても上手に歌を歌う",
                    "answer": "The girl of the green hair sings songs very well."
                },
                {
                    "question": "私は今季の新作アニメが楽しみです",
                    "answer": "I look forward to watching new anime in this season."
                },
                {
                    "question": "「あなたはどこの出身ですか？」「私は、英国出身デース！」",
                    "answer": "\"Where are you from?\" \"I am from UK.\""
                },
                {
                    "question": "あきらめたらそこで試合終了ですよ…？",
                    "answer": "When you give up, that's time when the game is over."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Part5 - 中2レベル5",
            "exercises": [
                {
                    "question": "クリスマスはいつですか？ 今年は中止しました。",
                    "answer": "When is Christmas? It is cancel this year."
                },
                {
                    "question": "どの娘が好きなんですか？",
                    "answer": "Which girls do you like?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "わけが分からないよ",
                    "answer": "It makes no sense at all!"
                },
                {
                    "question": "さあ、海賊の時間だ！",
                    "answer": "Come on. It's pirates time!"
                },
                {
                    "question": "あなたの兄は毎晩何時に狩りにいきますか？",
                    "answer": "What time dose your brother have a hunt every evening?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "「ごきげんよう」「ごきげんよう、お姉さま」",
                    "answer": "\"How are you?\" \"I'm fine. Thanks, big sister.\""
                },
                {
                    "question": "「あなたは何歳ですか？」「17歳です♪」「おいおい」",
                    "answer": "\"How old are you?\" \"I am saventeen years old.\" \"Are you joking?\""
                },
                {
                    "question": "「あなたの戦闘力はいくらですか？」「５３万です」",
                    "answer": "\"How much your power is?\" \"It is five hundred thirty thousand.\""
                },
                {
                    "question": "俺の妹がこんなに可愛いわけがない",
                    "answer": "My little sister can't be this cute!"
                },
                {
                    "question": "そうそう！も～っと私に頼っていいのよ！",
                    "answer": "Yes, you can count on me more and more!"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Part6 - 中2レベル6",
            "exercises": [
                {
                    "question": "あなたはサバンナで同じことを言うことが出来ますか？",
                    "answer": "Can you say the same thing in the Savanna?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "このアニメには男性が１人も居ません",
                    "answer": "There aren't any men in this anime."
                },
                {
                    "question": "分かったわ。あなたは私の敵ね。",
                    "answer": "I got it. you are my rival!"
                },
                {
                    "question": "くおえうえーーーるえうおおお",
                    "answer": "I am Chloe Lemaire."
                },
                {
                    "question": "ここって田舎なのん？",
                    "answer": "Is this the country?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "夏がくると沢山の人がコミケに行く",
                    "answer": "When summer comes, many people go to the Comic Market."
                },
                {
                    "question": "「その少女は成長して、何になりましたか？」 「魔女になりました」",
                    "answer": "\"What did the girl become when she grew up?\" \"She became a witch.\""
                },
                {
                    "question": "彼女は毎年2月27日に17歳になります",
                    "answer": "She will be seventeen years old in February 28th every year."
                },
                {
                    "question": "私が眠るとみんな死んじゃう",
                    "answer": "If I sleep, everyone will die."
                },
                {
                    "question": "「パワーをメテオに!」「いいですとも!」",
                    "answer": "\"Will you give your power to meteor please.\" \"Sure.\""
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Part7 - 中2レベル7",
            "exercises": [
                {
                    "question": "「僕にもゲームをかしてくれない？」 「悪いな。このゲーム、３人用なんだ」",
                    "answer": "\"Will you lend me your game please?\" \"I'm sorry. This is only for three persons.\""
                },
                {
                    "question": "主人公は幼馴染によって起こされなければなりません。",
                    "answer": "The main character must be waked up by childhood friend."
                },
                {
                    "question": "多くの場合、アニメの学生は戦わなくてはならない。",
                    "answer": "In many case, anime students have to battle."
                },
                {
                    "question": "世界線を超えることはとても難しい",
                    "answer": "It is very difficult to go over world line"
                },
                {
                    "question": "サラマンダーより、ずっとはやい!!",
                    "answer": "This is much faster than the salamander."
                },
                {
                    "question": "夏がくると沢山の人がコミケに行く",
                    "answer": "When summer comes, many people go to the Comic Market."
                },
                {
                    "question": "「そんな装備で大丈夫か？」 「一番いいのを頼む」",
                    "answer": "\"You sure that's enough armor?\" \"I'll take the best you have.\""
                },
                {
                    "question": "健康は命より大切です",
                    "answer": "Health is more important than life."
                },
                {
                    "question": "彼らは彼女に「世界一かわいいよ！」と言った",
                    "answer": "They said \"You are the most cute in the world.\" to her."
                },
                {
                    "question": "あなたは今までに何枚のパンを食べたか思い出すことができますか？",
                    "answer": "Can you remember how many slices of bread you have eaten until now?"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Part8 - 中2レベル8",
            "exercises": [
                {
                    "question": "一億年と二千年前から愛しています",
                    "answer": "I have loved you since one hundred million and two thousand years ago."
                },
                {
                    "question": "お兄ちゃんだけど愛さえあれば関係ないよねっ",
                    "answer": "As I love him, it is no problem that he is my brother, isn't it?"
                },
                {
                    "question": "ただしイケメンに限る",
                    "answer": "However it is permitted for only handsome man."
                },
                {
                    "question": "彼女は良い王であろうと努めています",
                    "answer": "She is trying to be a good king."
                },
                {
                    "question": "撃って良いのは撃たれる覚悟があるやつだけだ",
                    "answer": "Don’t shoot it at people, unless you get to be a better shot."
                },
                {
                    "question": "働きたくない。ぜったいに働きたくないでござる",
                    "answer": "I don't want to work. I'd never want to work."
                },
                {
                    "question": "彼女は運命に抗うために、何度も何度も同じ時間を繰り返します。",
                    "answer": "She relives the same time over and over again to resist the fate."
                },
                {
                    "question": "彼女は敵を倒すために絶唱を歌った。",
                    "answer": "She sang the superb song to beat the enemy."
                },
                {
                    "question": "彼女の歌は巨人たちを落ち着かせることができる。",
                    "answer": "Her song is able to calm the giants down."
                },
                {
                    "question": "彼女たちは歌うことで魔法を使うことができる。",
                    "answer": "They can use magic by singing songs."
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Part9 - 中2レベル9",
            "exercises": [
                {
                    "question": "何故かわからないが、最近の若者は戦艦に詳しい。",
                    "answer": "I don't know why, but recently young people are familiar with battleships."
                },
                {
                    "question": "駆逐してやる この世から・・・一匹・・・残らず。",
                    "answer": "I'll eradicate every single one of them from the world."
                },
                {
                    "question": "彼は前世を思い出すたびに強くなります。",
                    "answer": "He becomes more stronger when he remember his past life."
                },
                {
                    "question": "これらの動画を見るとき、彼らはいつも歌詞を聞き間違える。",
                    "answer": "They always make a mistake in lyrics when they watch these anime."
                },
                {
                    "question": "このアニメを見たので、私は自転車のサドルの高さを変えました。",
                    "answer": "I changed the height of the saddle of a bicycle because I watched this anime."
                },
                {
                    "question": "リンはレンと同じくらいの背の高さです。",
                    "answer": "Rin is as tall as Ren."
                },
                {
                    "question": "煩わしい太陽ね。",
                    "answer": "Good morning."
                },
                {
                    "question": "七つの大罪は聖騎士だったり、トリニティセブンだったり忙しい。",
                    "answer": "Seven deadly sins are very busy to become holy knights, Trinity Seven, and so on."
                },
                {
                    "question": "彼女たちは探偵というより農家に見えます。",
                    "answer": "They looks like rather a farmer than a detective."
                },
                {
                    "question": "",
                    "answer": "\"Would you like to get into a two-dimension world?\" \"I'd love to.\""
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}
